I love you.
Yoo Jung, keep the secret please.
My boyfriend would be wrongfully accused of committing hit-and-run.
I said I was driving the car, anyway.
So please help my lover.
I heard that he love her more than himself.
You are the prosecutor of this case
so you must comprehend it a lot.
It's said she died as a pregnant woman.
Kang Yoo Jung will receive the severest punishment.
I won't let my personal relationships affect my judgement.
It isn't that case.
What I want is to make sure that laws are fully applied.
Love? That's the only thing you want?
Ah, it is so pretty.
Sure.
You are lying.
If I'm lying, why am I with you?
Why are you with me, then?
Is that really important?
It looks good on you.
It means a lot to me.
What's wrong with you today?
I want my boy tell me that "I love you".
Is that wrong?
Hey! Ji Hee!
Ji Hee!
Ji Hee! I get it. I love you.
I say I love you.
I love you.
You know me, right?
Min Hyuk has an eye for girls.
Be nice to him. He's emotionally fragile.
Okay.
You have to dump this pretty lady
to accept the marriage settled by your father.
You must be upset. Am I right?
Madam!
Why? You have not be frank to her yet?
- Ji Hee! - Let her go if you can not give her a promise.
She is chic.
If she's scared of me,
how can she handle your father?
Do not ruin the life of a young lady
for your own selfishness.
Why take it so seriously？
Just be your father's good boy.
Congressmen Shin holds the absolute authority.
Nothing could stop him.
Your father never accept no-good trades.
I'm not in the mood for this kind of crap.
As for Se Yeon, buy her if you need; sell her if not.
That's called mergers and acquisitions.
Marriage is the same case.
Will you be happy if marry your wife like that?
Idiot! Is happiness important?
Seo Ji Hee, is that the name?
You shouldn't have taken her seriously.
If you have dumped her earlier, she would not be so heart-broken.
How dare you...
Girls are everywhere.
Shut up.
Look at you!
Why did you fall for a cheap girl like that
and put yourself in this mess?
Hey! What are you doing? Asshole!
How dare you talk like that?
You, you bastard!
Let me go!
Asshole!
Hey! Be a grown man, Jo Min Hyuk!
Loser, you couldn't even protect your own girl.
- Let me go! - Hey hey hey!
Asshole! God damn asshole! Let me go!
He still couldn't pull himself together?
Chairman, why don't you leave him alone this time?
What?
He is a young man now,
yet I haven't given him good lessons.
Whenever he cried over a broken toy,
I always got him a new one,
instead of snatching all his toys away.
Gwang Min!
Yes, chairman.
Stop giving him any support.
Sorry?
He'll not realize how lucky he has been
until loses everything.
What kind of losing do you think is unbearable for him?
What do you mean I can't sell it?
Because you are the most powerful shareful stockholder of Highland,
so you are prohibited from selling the stocks in your own name.
Even though they're mine?
Without the permission of the board, the trade is invalid.
I'm Ahn Do Hoon, the prosecutor of this case.
In accordance with the Telecommunications Act,
all the conversations will be recorded from now.
Your name is Kang Yoo Jung and you were born on July 20th, 1984.
You live in No. 21 Samseon-dong, Seongbuk-gu, right?
Yes.
You are entitled to appoint an attorney.
Do you want one?
No, I am good.
Between 10 p.m. and 11 p.m. on the night of 23rd,
were you driving on National Road No.8?
I was.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung.
You have to tell me nothing but the truth here.
It's not too late. Let's tell the truth.
Look! Look!
We've asked all the questions already. Why does he bother to interrogate again?
He should make her plead guilty here.
He's a newbie. Let's wait and see.
She's the guilty one, sir.
I can tell the guilty guys by just one glance into their eyes.
Their eyes would never lie.
Innocent guys would never look away.
Only dishonest ones can't bear direct eye contacts.
Look! Look! Look at her.
She can't look into his eyes. She dares not.
Again. Were you really driving the car?
Yes. I was.
Anyway, you will be back soon.
Just save our troubles by staying around.
Chief. It's unfortunate that the victims were dead,
yet it's reasonable to doubt that
the girl isn't the infringer.
Rather than charge her in haste, why can we wait and see...
What's your point?
The defendat wasn't aware of the accident.
The defendat fixed the blood-stained car before runnng away.
What makes you believe that she wasn't aware of the accident?
-The suspect is... -You're the prosecutor.
You have to look at the facts instead of one-sided stories of a suspect.
If you want to defend her against all the evidence,
to be her attorney.
I heard you received a Chief Juetice Award at the graduate ceremony of academy.
I did.
Hundreds of officials behind you are waiting to be promoted.
If I put them in charge of the case,
do you think they would come to me like you?
The police have found all the evidence and submitted the charges.
If you cann't handle it, leave here.
Seek an arrest warrant right away.
Waiting for what? Hop in!
Hey. How is your day? Want something to eat?
Daddy!
Why being so sticky.
Your daughter is leaving for Japan. Isn't it cool?
Really? When?
Maybe this week if nothing stops me. Yet I have to wait until everything is settled.
This week? What did Do Hoon say?
He supports me of course. We can marry after my return.
Is there something wrong between you?
No. Nothing is wrong.
Anyway, you should close your store and date with me tomorrow.
Is that clear?
Do you have to wander around just before your marriage?
Are your in-laws okay with it?
Don't be silly. People aren't that conservative at this year.
Have they talked about dowary?
Don't keep all that troubles to yourself.
If you need anything, let me know.
As I said, everything is fine.
What? What did you say? I would rat on you?
My son's a prosecutor.
Is that possible I can't repay that bit of money?
That's what you boast of whenever and wherever.
Huh, if your son is that impressive,
why are you living like in this way?
If he finds out that his mother isn't paying other's money back,
he the prosecutor must be happy.
Hey, are you finised?
Oho oho, did you just hit me?
You'll be dead. Hey!
What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry. - Why are you apologizing?
They're the one that should apologize.
Why shoud you nod and bow here?
I'm not going to be submissive any longer.
Let's go back! Go!
Forgive us.
My son's a prosecutor.
Why would I keep eyes upon your bit of money.
Then pay me back now.
Don't lend her any money again.
I have no money to lend her.
She is disturbing all us.
Why's the good to fight as neighbors?
You are here?
Don't nag your mom any more.
Anyway, it's my incapacity to be blamed for your mom's doing.
I might sound old-fashioned,
but this is how I feel.
Only a powerful man could give his woman a happy life.
Don't take my road.
You won't of course.
My son is a prosecutor, he will be fine.
Dad.
You'll be late for work. Hurrry up.
I still can't believe that I have a son like you.
Have a good day.
Excuse me. You can't park here.
Drive away quickly please.
Get it.
Excuse me!
I've to close the door to meet with my daughter.
I meed to meet with your daughter too.
You know Yoo Jung? Do you work with her?
She cann't be back soon.
That's a problem.
Umm. Please take some snacks.
It's made by Yoo Jung.
It's very yummy that would be popular in Japan.
Could you please send a word to Yoo Jung that I'm here to repay my debt.
And I'll be here again.
Excuse me!
Oh! Hi!
What can I do for you?
A man asked me to give you this.
What man?
He is over there.
Dad, try this on.
Again?
Ah, it's hot. Too hot.
Isn't it?
Why are we here in a hot summer day?
Down jackets are supposed to be bought in hot days.
You've been talking about buying a new down jacket for years. Now it's the time.
What do you think?
Is it too thin?
Thank you.
Please have more.
This store has ads on TV shows frequently.
It's a good one.
All the food is the same as long as it enters your stomach.
How much do you pay for those?
Let's go to the movies.
Daddy, Isn't it ages since your last time in a theatre.
Stop behaving like this please.
Sorry?
You don't have to spent money for me. After being married, you would see that life is tougher.
I see.
Do you come to places like this a lot?
It's hard to make money, but easy to spend it.
Could you please stop nagging me if you want to hang out with me again.
I'm not going to buy your blame by my money.
Then go getting married, if you hate my nag.
I will. Don't you worry.
By that time you should date a nice woman.
It's sorrow to see you as a single at this age.
Look at Do Hoon. You see man would look handsome after dressing up.
Please hurry up.
After your marriage I'll look for my chance. I need no lessons.
You are the reason for my being single all those years.
I've a job, I own a store.
I'm worse than nobody.
By the way,
some guy came to the store to repay his debt.
Debt?
What debt?
It's about 20000KRW.
What's the collateral?
He said will be back for it.
Hey, you!
Yes, the toll is 8000KRW, please.
And agency fee is 15000KRW.
Aha, you take it as a collateral.
Take a good care of it. I would redeem it back.
It's nothing. Don't worry. Let's move.
Good job. Everyone has done their best.
How is it going?
Yes, chairman.
Let's go!
Money helps you again?
You are here right now. I guess it works.
That's how you treated Ji Hee?
Snatched away everything she had to made her give up?
You think K Corporation is just a street store?
K Corporation is a company with tens of thousands of employees to support.
I'm not energetic enough to care about her.
You knew that she was pregnant with my child.
Why cann't you give me a child that I expect of.
You've been playing around enough.
It's time to win Se Yeon's heart.
You care nothing about my feeling, don't you?
I don't want to repeat what I said.
Who do you think has been paying your expenses all these years?
Can't you think of me as your son for just a moment?
Persuade him to keep away from any trouble.
When the project is finished,
we would overlook buildings over there.
You bring me up here to tell me that?
Holy crap.
Your father started from nothing.
He saved me from casino,
helped me get rid of my nasty father and gave me a chance to work for him.
Gwang Min! I'm not interested.
Save your performance to my dad.
Min Hyuk.
Your father has devoted his whole life to his family and company.
You should feel lucky that he is your father, not your opponent.
What a submissive dog dad has kept.
Why so obedient?
Those are Seo Ji Hee's possessions.
How dare you touch them?
Do whatever you want with them.
Dog should act like a dog.
Don't try to interfere with human businesses.
Don't blame your father for what happened to Ji Hee.
You're the one who killed her.
Shut up!
You killed her.
This wouldn't have happened, if you'd let her go earlier.
Now she died with your child.
She at least tried to protect her child.
What did you do?
You are a loser.
You just happen to be born in a rich family.
Shut up!
You want to win?
Then stop hidding away. Return to your home.
What are you crying about if you lack the courage to join the battle?
That's just awful.
Ji Hee!
Ji Hee, I'm sorry that I didn't keep my word.
Sorry that I didn't protect you and our baby.
I'll suffer what you suffered and won't love any woman again.
I'll compensate you with my misery.
I promise you.
I'll kick the murder into the hell.
Se Yeon.
What are you doing here?
I'm just here to see you.
Lying again.
You're unbelievable!
You want to die again? Is it why you are here?
No.
I want to live this time.
We are supposed to be blind to each other, aren't we?
I thought I was following my heart.
Yet I just find out what I'm capable of is ordering food in restaurants.
You didn't see it until now?
Nothing's free.
Why don't we take parents' advices as soon as possible?
What are you doing?
Se Yeon, marry me.
I wish I could decide it.
I'll do my best to satisfy your requirements.
Marry me.
Satisfy my requirements?
Such as what?
Freedom.
You've the freedom to do whatever you want to do.
That's what I'll satisfy you with.
Date whoever you want. I won't care.
You don't have to have babies. Just marry me.
When my old man dies, we'll divorce.
Are you crazy?
That's all I have.
I thought I have nothing but money.
But I was wrong.
Se Yeon, please help me out, just once.
Thank you.
Finally.
Now you see who gives you all that you need.
Very well.
Min Hyuk.
How could you ask Min Joo for money?
You should've come to me first.
Do you think it's your money?
It's dad's.
Min Hyuk!
Min Joo, you should be obedient to dad with all your heart.
Once against him, you'll face the doomsday.
You might be kicked off the house naked.
Min Hyuk, he's doing it for your sake.
He's doing it for his company. You cann't see it?
Or you just pretend that you know nothing of it.
Dad.
I'll marry Se Yeon in line with you wish.
Then what's my award from it?
What?
This marriage is a business for you. I think I deserve a share.
Fine. Tell me what you want.
I want the hotel.
Her brother is taking over the casino of the hotel.
And she's taking over the theater in the hotel.
I feel like to give a hand as well.
Min Hyuk, that's just...
Good. Then start from the scratch.
When you are recognized by members of the council,
the hotel is yours.
If there is nothing else, please excuse me.
You might feel down for losing the hotel.
Min Hyuk!
These are the documents of K Corporation.
Have you surveyed Prosecutor Ahn?
Yoo Jung, when I was a middle school student,
my dad had one leg fractured by a folklift
in a demonstration against unfair dismissal.
He was sued for vandalism
before receiving proper medical treatments.
That company dumped dad. Yet mum spent 10 years paying the compensation claimed by it.
I wanted to change it. Yet it's always powerless ones' fault.
And it's rebellious ones' fault as well,
I wanted to show them that everyone is equal in front of the law.
Dear, you can do it.
That's why you've working so hard.
You really think so? Do you think I can make it by framing you?
How could I be so mean?
Dear, it was a tragic accident.
Both for her and for us.
Yoo Jung. Don't you ever regret meeting me?
Not at all. People who have a future never regret.
We have a future, don't we?
Yoo Jung. Sorry.
Stop saying sorry to each other please.
That was an unfortunate accident.
She had no chance to feel regret. We should feel sorry for him.
-Excuse me. Have you seen my dad? -No.
Dad!
Dad...
Case number 521. Since Kang Yoo Jung, the defendant of the hit and run case, don't show up for questioning,
this court issues a warrant for her arrest.
Dad.
Why are you here?
Why didn't you tell me where you were going?
Your phone is left at home. I was worried... that something terrible might have happened.
I was so worried!
Relax. I came here because I miss your mother.
Mom. Sorry I haven't been here more often.
It's okay. You're too busy with your wedding.
Have some.
The cream that I made yesterday is really good.
Your mother loved my cream buns.
During the cancer treatment, she vomited what she had,
except my cream buns.
I brought those here and hope you mum could taste them befor they getting cold.
I want her to know that you're getting married with gracious.
You mum held your hands till the last moment.
She cried a lot because she can't accompany you any longer.
Miyeong, don't worry. Our daughter grows well.
Look at her. You should praise me.
-Ms. Kang Yoo Jung. -Dad, please get inside.
-What's going on? -I'll be back.
Ms. Kang, you must know why you're under arrest?
What's going on? What is it, Yoo Jung?
She didn't show up for questioning, so we're here to arrest her.
- You've the right to hire an attorney. And you've the right to remain silent. -Yoo Jung! - Dad!
- Anything said by you from this moment... - Yoo Jung
- might be used as evidence against you in the court. - Yoo Jung
Keep off. Let's go.
Yoo Jung Yoo Jung..Yoo Jung..Yoo Jung..
Dad Dad ..
Dad ..Dad .. Dad ..
Do Hoon, wait a minute. Do Hoon,..suddenly..
- Come this way. - OK, listen...
What? Death? Yoo Jung killed someone?
Is that possible?
It was an accident. She didn't mean to kill her.
- Dad. - No. Something's wrong.
Yoo Jung... Ok, even if she'd hit someone,
she wouldn't have run away like that.
You know that better than me, Do Hoon.
That's not true. They must be mistaken.
I'm going to go and tell them. She didn't do it.
Dad, I'm the prosecutor of Yoo Jung's case.
Thank god. That's good news.
Yes. I'll do whatever to help her.
But if you come to me like this, it won't help Yoo Jung.
If they find out what's going on between Yoo Jung and I, I'll be ruled out from this case.
So you can't come to me.
Then... what should I do?
The best solution is to settle with the victim's family out of court.
Yes, you are right.
Dad. Dad you have to cheer up.
I'll give you my hand behind you, but I can't openly support Yoo Jung.
- I understand. Yoo Jung must be really scared right now - Sorry.
No. No. It's not your fault.
Please take good care of her.
I won't let my personal relationships affect my judgement.
I wonder what he meant by that.
What are you doing here?
I told you.
I'm here to make sure that laws are fully applied.
We are conducting investigations with all efforts.
Please don't worry. You could be back right now.
I was not intended to worry about it.
I don't know why I'm so worried.
I guess it's because our prosecutor has to refresh himself with crappy coffee.
Why are you so tired? Because you were working late?
Or because I should have given you a car.
Prosecutor, I heard that you've a lover?
Maybe you didn't mention it.
What's your point?
What kind of love deserves to be called true love?
I thought Ji Hee and I was in deep love,
but people told me that wasn't love.
I love her, truely.
So I'm going to prove it to her
how much I love her.
I'll wait and see.
I'm watching you, Prosecutor Ahn.
Open her cuffs, please.
Prosecutor.
Ms. Kang.
There is no evidence to prove your innocence till now.
Are you still pleading not guilty?
Something is wrong about dad.
Answer my question please.
Dad hasn't come to see me.
Not even once.
That doesn't like him.
He said he's been having bad headaches recently. Prosecutor.
Admit your guilt, anyway.
And apologize to the victim's family please.
If you admit your crime, the court will grant you a clemency.
I understand.
I don't care what will fall upon me.
And I'm really sorry for that tragedy.
I'm sorry for the death.
But I...
I'm worried about my dad.
I think he's really sick.
I couldn't take him to a doctor.
Prosecutor. Prosector.
Kang Yoo Jung.
Are you guilty?
Dad must be sick severely.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung!
My dad is sick!
Kang Yoo Jung, look at this.
Don't worry. I'll take care of him.
Come in. Have a seat.
What are you talking about?
A hit and run? People died?
Yoo Jung...
I come to you because...
I've little savings in hand.
So I want to borrow some from you.
In order to settle the case out of court,
I've to prepare a large sum of money.
Does Do Hoon know this?
He told me to reconciliate with the victim's family.
Take this.
I'll try to collect the rest.
Er...
You said Yoo Jung was in jail.
We have to bail her immediately.
How could a young lady stayed in jail?
She is right. Please take it.
I'll go around to see what I can do.
It'll be okay.
Thank you. I'm going to beg for pardon.
Ok. Take it easy please.
Thank you.
We are family.
No wander they are a bit queer recently.
You just impressed me.
With so much money, they can complain no more I guess.
She hit and ran?
Does she mean to ruin everyone?
Could she think like a normal man?
Dear!
Stop defending her. She's a murder!
Don't you know what Do Hoon's job is?
His job is to defend the dead ones.
I beg you accept it.
Madam, Yoo Jung was brought up by myself.
Her mother died when she was five.
After that I raised her all alone.
I could understand all your feelings.
Sorry.
I know no matter how many times I keel to beg your pardon,
our sin could never be washed away.
Your daughter lost her life.
She was so young.
I konw nothing could compensate your loss.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'am willing to do anything if you agree to settle it out of court.
She's getting married soon.
Please give her a chance.
After your daughter killed my daughter,
you ask me to keep her alive?
You are a parent too. You brought up a girl as well.
You want me to forgive my daughter's murder?
I'm sorry, I...
My poor daughter lay on the cold road for hours and hours,
because your precious daughter ran away after hitting her.
As long as I think of how Ji Hee died,
I would rather tear up the murder into pieces.
Now you want to settle it?
All those stuffs are meaningless.
No matter how many you bring here, I won't give you the permission.
No matter what you bring here,
I won't settle it in private.
Leave here with all your money.
You bring back my daughter.
All rise!
Be seated!
Now the Seoul District Court holds a criminal trial.
Case number 521. A hit-and-run.
Please step forward, Kang Yoo Jung the defendant.
Do Hoon, do you remember the day we met?
I waited for you at the bus stop
after you left by bus,
because I got a hunch that you would return for me.
After 10 minutes or so,
you rushed back.
Of course I remember.
I was not sure why I would run back.
I just thought you might be waiting for me.
Don't worry, I'm always here.
No rush is needed.
Just walk to me and take me away as you did.
Kang Yoo Jung's irresponsible act
took the life of a young woman
and an unborn baby.
This, under no circumstance, is excusable.
Therefore, as the prosecutor,
I sentence Kang Yoo Jung to jail for 5 years.
Good work, prosecutor Ahn.
Actually you did better than I expected.
Put aside any personal feelings, and follow the law.
Am I talking too much?
What's your point on earth?
Ahn Do Hoon is speaking.
This is hospital. Do you know Mr. Kang Woo Chul?
No. 2008, get in!
Hey! Get up.
Why are you here?
Introduce yourself. It's the rule.
How many times have you been here?
Excuse me?
She committed hit and run. Someone died.
You killed people.
What do you want?
Shut up.
Do it!
Beat her.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Stop! Stop!
How is she?
What's it?
2008 2008
Wake up, 2008, 2008.
2008 2008 2008
Is your menstruation normal?
When was the last time of it?
Excuse me?
You didn't know you were pregnant?
Are you a blockhead?
Do you have anyone to contact with?
What?
Kang Yoo Jung is pregnant?
It's getting interesting.
Push harder!
Good! I can see the head.
It's almost done.
Look.
Next on Secret Love
Leave.
Do Hoon, he's a big boy now.
San, say thank you.
Say it.
You know she is releasing soon.
You have a parole review next week. Be a good girl.
2008, the defendant of the hit and run case.
Even a prosecutor would corrupt?
What do you want from me?
Leave her.
Just stay in the jail, forever.
You would be a trouble once you are out.
Please welcome Jo Min Hyuk, the new chairman.
Take him away.
No!
Yoo Jung!
You can't!
Don't, please.